Block buster did not die
because people
stopped loving movies
It died because the
business model was
built around a world
where inconven ience
was profitable
Late fees were not just
annoying
They were part of the
machine
Netflix attacked the
pain point first
No due dates no store
trip and
no late fee surprise
Then Block buster had
debt
thousands of stores and
a digital shift
it could not out run
By 2010 the old rental
empire filed
for bankruptcy
The lesson is not that
Netflix was
magic
It is that a better
customer experience
can make the old profit
center disappear
Save this for the next
time someone
says Netflix killed it
overnight