MY SISTER TOLD THE
WHOLE FAMILY I OWED
HER FREE WEDDING PHOTOS,
SO I CANCELLED TWO
DAYS BEFORE THE EVENT.
I SHOOT PORTRAITS ON
WEEKENDS, BUT I AM
NOT A FULL-TIME WEDDING
PHOTOGRAPHER AND I TOLD
HER THAT FROM THE
START.
WE AGREED I WOULD
DO A TINY COURTHOUSE
PACKAGE FOR A DISCOUNT,
NOT A FULL DAY,
NOT EDITS FOR A
HUNDRED GUESTS, AND DEFINITELY
NOT FOR FREE.
THEN SHE STARTED TEXTING
ME SHOT LISTS AT
MIDNIGHT, ADDED A REHEARSAL
DINNER, AND TOLD MY
MOM I HAD ALREADY
PROMISED EVERYTHING.
AT A FAMILY LUNCH
SHE LITERALLY SAID, IF
YOU LOVED ME YOU
WOULD NOT CHARGE ME,
AND EVERYONE STARED AT
ME LIKE I WAS
THE VILLAIN.
SO I REFUNDED HER
DEPOSIT ON THE SPOT,
SENT ONE MESSAGE SAYING
I WAS OUT, AND
TOLD HER TO HIRE
SOMEONE WHO ACTUALLY WANTED
THE JOB.
NOW HALF THE FAMILY
SAYS I HUMILIATED HER
BEFORE THE WEDDING, AND
THE OTHER HALF SAYS
SHE TREATED ME LIKE
FREE STAFF WITH A
CAMERA.
BE HONEST, WAS CANCELLING
CRUEL, OR WAS SHE
JUST TRYING TO BULLY
ME INTO UNPAID WORK?