My sister texted me at twelve
fourteen and asked is Liam with you
right now I said yes why and
she sent back then look at what
he sent me The screenshot was his
name at the top and one line
that just said you awake An hour
earlier he told me he was exhausted
and going straight to sleep So I
asked why he was in her DMs
after midnight He answered instantly relax that
is an old screenshot
Then my sister sent the full thread
and the excuse died on the next
line He had typed does she ever
check your phone like I was the
problem I forwarded
that line back to him and watched
the typing bubble start and stop Then
every draft vanished my last message failed
and his profile disappeared My sister just
texted well that answers that Would you
stay after this