My roommate staged fake
work calls for months,
so I replaced the set
with the real thing.
He kept telling his
parents he was crushing
his remote job, but every
video call happened
at the same fake desk in
our living
room with a dead laptop
and a blank spreadsheet.
The weird part was that
he made me
stay quiet in the
background, like I was
an extra in the lie,
while his parents
bragged about him to the
whole family.
Then I found out he had
actually been
fired months earlier and
was burning through rent
money, so I ordered a
cheap real monitor,
keyboard, and lamp and
rebuilt the setup before
the next call.
When his parents called,
he sat down expecting
the usual performance,
saw the real setup, and
completely panicked
because now he either had
to tell the truth or
explain why the
lie suddenly looked
professional.
He says I humiliated him,
but I think
I forced the lie to end
before he
wrecked his finances even
more, so tell me
if that was helpful or
way out of line.
Was I helping, or did I
cross the line?