How can stocks hit records
while oil still swings like
a warning siren?
On April twenty
fourth, Intel
jumped twenty
three point six
percent after a strong
quarter, and
that helped push the S
and P five hundred and
Nasdaq to
records. But oil was
reacting to a
different story:
traders were
watching the Strait of
Hormuz, where
any disruption
can squeeze a huge global
supply route.
Washington also
said it would not renew
Iranian oil
waivers, which
kept pressure on
energy expectations
even before
diplomacy looked
shakier. Then
ceasefire talks
wobbled when the
planned Pakistan
trip for U.S.
envoys was
canceled, so
stocks kept
celebrating earnings
while oil kept pricing war
risk. Follow for fast
plain-English market breakdowns.