An EF-4 tornado tore through
Enid, Oklahoma, and the shocking
part is that no one
died. This was not a
near miss.
The storm packed one hundred
seventy to one hundred seventy
five mile per hour winds
and carved a violent path
straight through town.
It stayed on the ground
for about nine miles, stretched
roughly five hundred yards wide,
and damaged around forty homes
in and around Enid.
Emergency crews searched homes, pulled
trapped residents out, and officials
said the city somehow escaped
with only minor injuries
instead of mass casualties.
That is why this story
matters. Usually when damage looks
this severe, there are deaths.
Enid got extremely lucky.
The lesson is not that
the storm was weaker than
it looked.
The lesson is that preparation,
shelter, and response made the
difference when the worst case
almost happened.
Preparation is boring right up
until it saves a town.